[
  {
    "question": "29 - 39 =",
    "correct": -10,
    "choices": [
      1,
      21,
      -10,
      -99
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "93 - 44 =",
    "correct": 49,
    "choices": [
      78,
      49,
      81,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "95 - 87 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      17,
      12,
      8,
      -58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "61 - 76 =",
    "correct": -15,
    "choices": [
      64,
      -15,
      25,
      4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "77 - 44 =",
    "correct": 33,
    "choices": [
      33,
      10,
      -33,
      -58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "51 - 82 =",
    "correct": -31,
    "choices": [
      52,
      34,
      -77,
      -31
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "66 - 62 =",
    "correct": 4,
    "choices": [
      4,
      -94,
      34,
      68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "58 - 23 =",
    "correct": 35,
    "choices": [
      35,
      -37,
      -25,
      50
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 30 =",
    "correct": 51,
    "choices": [
      51,
      43,
      83,
      72
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 60 =",
    "correct": 21,
    "choices": [
      21,
      -50,
      -39,
      -73
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "61 - 88 =",
    "correct": -27,
    "choices": [
      -50,
      -3,
      -27,
      -58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "53 - 72 =",
    "correct": -19,
    "choices": [
      -45,
      -19,
      -56,
      -6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 - 24 =",
    "correct": -9,
    "choices": [
      17,
      -9,
      -41,
      -90
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "38 - 67 =",
    "correct": -29,
    "choices": [
      -29,
      -34,
      -16,
      -87
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "66 - 35 =",
    "correct": 31,
    "choices": [
      63,
      31,
      -42,
      -51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "36 - 18 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      -58,
      -64,
      18,
      -22
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "99 - 73 =",
    "correct": 26,
    "choices": [
      -27,
      -52,
      38,
      26
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 - 58 =",
    "correct": -41,
    "choices": [
      -54,
      -84,
      -41,
      -69
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "26 - 90 =",
    "correct": -64,
    "choices": [
      -55,
      -64,
      -78,
      41
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "31 - 16 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      15,
      53,
      -84,
      -88
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 - 45 =",
    "correct": -33,
    "choices": [
      -56,
      -79,
      -84,
      -33
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 - 92 =",
    "correct": -72,
    "choices": [
      -89,
      -72,
      77,
      82
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "27 - 20 =",
    "correct": 7,
    "choices": [
      -86,
      -19,
      7,
      37
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "23 - 18 =",
    "correct": 5,
    "choices": [
      5,
      -79,
      -99,
      21
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "47 - 35 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      -87,
      12,
      50,
      19
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "21 - 94 =",
    "correct": -73,
    "choices": [
      68,
      27,
      -73,
      -57
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "28 - 70 =",
    "correct": -42,
    "choices": [
      -42,
      75,
      2,
      -1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "83 - 48 =",
    "correct": 35,
    "choices": [
      -17,
      70,
      35,
      -43
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "66 - 24 =",
    "correct": 42,
    "choices": [
      76,
      41,
      42,
      57
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 - 68 =",
    "correct": -55,
    "choices": [
      87,
      -31,
      61,
      -55
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "64 - 25 =",
    "correct": 39,
    "choices": [
      17,
      -62,
      39,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "88 - 44 =",
    "correct": 44,
    "choices": [
      44,
      -65,
      -15,
      35
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "92 - 28 =",
    "correct": 64,
    "choices": [
      -6,
      -93,
      45,
      64
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "35 - 27 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      -27,
      24,
      87,
      8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "43 - 18 =",
    "correct": 25,
    "choices": [
      -41,
      -99,
      25,
      -89
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "60 - 20 =",
    "correct": 40,
    "choices": [
      40,
      -97,
      45,
      -68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 - 83 =",
    "correct": -70,
    "choices": [
      -70,
      -14,
      72,
      57
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "58 - 59 =",
    "correct": -1,
    "choices": [
      -15,
      -1,
      -73,
      -46
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "22 - 85 =",
    "correct": -63,
    "choices": [
      45,
      -63,
      93,
      -94
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "80 - 38 =",
    "correct": 42,
    "choices": [
      42,
      -1,
      -65,
      24
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "66 - 69 =",
    "correct": -3,
    "choices": [
      -42,
      -14,
      -74,
      -3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "89 - 30 =",
    "correct": 59,
    "choices": [
      -56,
      -44,
      59,
      49
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "67 - 15 =",
    "correct": 52,
    "choices": [
      -56,
      97,
      52,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "87 - 94 =",
    "correct": -7,
    "choices": [
      1,
      89,
      -29,
      -7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "80 - 48 =",
    "correct": 32,
    "choices": [
      6,
      75,
      32,
      -2
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "79 - 78 =",
    "correct": 1,
    "choices": [
      -62,
      76,
      81,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "52 - 37 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      33,
      15,
      68,
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 22 =",
    "correct": 59,
    "choices": [
      48,
      -58,
      15,
      59
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "40 - 98 =",
    "correct": -58,
    "choices": [
      -58,
      -76,
      84,
      58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "37 - 71 =",
    "correct": -34,
    "choices": [
      91,
      63,
      38,
      -34
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 - 46 =",
    "correct": -31,
    "choices": [
      13,
      96,
      -31,
      5
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "67 - 32 =",
    "correct": 35,
    "choices": [
      -8,
      -77,
      35,
      -96
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "46 - 53 =",
    "correct": -7,
    "choices": [
      -7,
      -46,
      86,
      27
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "66 - 92 =",
    "correct": -26,
    "choices": [
      57,
      5,
      -26,
      -44
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "50 - 32 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      -96,
      57,
      -86,
      18
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 - 92 =",
    "correct": -77,
    "choices": [
      16,
      82,
      -85,
      -77
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "96 - 70 =",
    "correct": 26,
    "choices": [
      -42,
      100,
      10,
      26
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "91 - 32 =",
    "correct": 59,
    "choices": [
      -82,
      22,
      -98,
      59
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "66 - 23 =",
    "correct": 43,
    "choices": [
      -6,
      43,
      -11,
      -9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "94 - 99 =",
    "correct": -5,
    "choices": [
      -5,
      -52,
      35,
      -30
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "73 - 45 =",
    "correct": 28,
    "choices": [
      28,
      73,
      41,
      51
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "93 - 53 =",
    "correct": 40,
    "choices": [
      50,
      -37,
      24,
      40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 - 60 =",
    "correct": -41,
    "choices": [
      93,
      -41,
      -33,
      -80
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "80 - 95 =",
    "correct": -15,
    "choices": [
      -69,
      -51,
      77,
      -15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "89 - 20 =",
    "correct": 69,
    "choices": [
      -77,
      69,
      1,
      79
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "68 - 21 =",
    "correct": 47,
    "choices": [
      47,
      83,
      -45,
      -14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "68 - 95 =",
    "correct": -27,
    "choices": [
      -27,
      65,
      56,
      -90
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "13 - 78 =",
    "correct": -65,
    "choices": [
      96,
      95,
      -65,
      -56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "49 - 64 =",
    "correct": -15,
    "choices": [
      -18,
      -52,
      -15,
      68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "68 - 51 =",
    "correct": 17,
    "choices": [
      17,
      78,
      -8,
      -10
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "54 - 87 =",
    "correct": -33,
    "choices": [
      -69,
      55,
      -68,
      -33
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "80 - 72 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      8,
      -89,
      -81,
      -58
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "59 - 59 =",
    "correct": 0,
    "choices": [
      -92,
      -45,
      98,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "22 - 30 =",
    "correct": -8,
    "choices": [
      -38,
      30,
      18,
      -8
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 - 43 =",
    "correct": -31,
    "choices": [
      -31,
      -16,
      -74,
      -91
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 56 =",
    "correct": 25,
    "choices": [
      -70,
      21,
      25,
      -91
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "96 - 53 =",
    "correct": 43,
    "choices": [
      83,
      43,
      -26,
      6
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "86 - 83 =",
    "correct": 3,
    "choices": [
      3,
      94,
      -20,
      -39
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "22 - 24 =",
    "correct": -2,
    "choices": [
      -27,
      47,
      -2,
      -68
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "68 - 20 =",
    "correct": 48,
    "choices": [
      48,
      57,
      79,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "59 - 98 =",
    "correct": -39,
    "choices": [
      -39,
      -7,
      -1,
      57
    ]
  }
]
